Connecticut Women of the United Church of Christ records, 1928-2020.
Congregational Library & Archives
- District records, 1928 2011; 1928-2011; 79 Folders; 6 Volumes
  - Hartford district records, 1928 2007; 1928-2007; 26 Folders; 1 Volume
    - Annual meeting, 1959 1974; 1959-1974 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Other district records, 1959 1976; 1959-1976 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Event date lists, 1959 1983; 1959-1983 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Program announcements, 1959 1995; 1959-1995, undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Officer ballots, 1960 1980; 1960-1980 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Executive Board records, 1960 1973; 1960-1973 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Archival Notebook #2B, held by Recording Secretary, 1974 1988; 1974-1988 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Archival Notebook #2B, held by Recording Secretary, 1974 1988; 1974-1988 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Officer notebook, 1974 1993; 1974-1993 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Board member manual, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - How-to's Handbook for Vice-President, 1988 1989; 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Archival Notebook, Volume #1, held by President, 1988 1994; 1988-1994 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Archival Notebook, Volume #1, held by President, 1988 1994; 1988-1994 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Archival Notebook, Volume #1, held by President, 1988 1994; 1988-1994 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Archival Notebook, Volume #1, held by President, 1988 1994; 1988-1994 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Archival Notebook #2B, held by Recording Secretary, 1988 1996; 1988-1996 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Notebook, 1991 2007; 1991-2007 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Financial records, 2002 2005; 2002-2005, undated (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Eastern district records, 1928 2011; 1928-2011; 14 Folders
    This subseries contains the records of the Eastern district, including district officer lists and ballots, mailing lists, lists of event dates, program announcements, meeting programs, and an annual report.
    - Bulletins, 1928 1934; 1928-1934 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Officer lists, 1938 1991; 1938-1991 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Mailing lists, 1957 1979; 1957-1979 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Event date lists, 1958 1978; 1958-1978 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Program announcements, 1958 1969; 1958-1969, undated (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Program announcements, 1970 2009; 1970-2009, undated (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Meeting programs, 1959 2010; 1959-2010 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Other district records, 1960 2011; 1960-2011, undated (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Annual meetings, 1961 1970; 1961-1970 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Officer ballots, 1962 1980; 1962-1980 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Annual report, 1964 1965; 1964-1965 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Board meetings, 1967 2006; 1967-2006 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Executive Board meetings, 1968 1969; 1968-1969 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - By-laws, undated (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - New Haven district records, 1928 1980; 1928-1980; 12 Folders; 2 Volumes
    This subseries contains the records of the New Haven district, including district officer lists and ballots, mailing lists, lists of event dates, program announcements, meeting programs, annual reports, scrapbooks, and photographs. The New Haven district became the Southwestern district in 1973, and records of the Southwestern district can be found in the Southwestern district subseries.
    - Bulletins, 1928 1933; 1928-1933, undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Officer lists, 1930 1973; 1930-1973 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - New Haven district scrapbook, 1935 1967; 1935-1967 (Box 9, Volume 3)
    - Mailing lists, 1957 1973; 1957-1973 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Annual meeting, 1960 1969; 1960-1969 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Meeting programs, 1960 1973; 1960-1973 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Program announcements, 1961 1972; 1961-1972, undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Officer ballots, 1962 1973; 1962-1973 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Other district records, 1962 1980; 1962-1980, undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Annual report drafts, 1963 1965; 1963-1965 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Event date lists, 1963 1973; 1963-1973 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Materials removed from New Haven district scrapbook, 1964 1975; 1964-1975 (Box 6, Folder 11)
      Items in this folder were removed from New Haven district scrapbook, 1968-1975, located in the District records series, New Haven district records subseries.
    - New Haven district scrapbook, 1968 1975; 1968-1975 (Box 9, Volume 5)
      Materials removed from this scrapbook can be found in Materials removed from New Haven district scrapbook, 1964-1975 and Photographs removed from New Haven district scrapbook, 1971, undated. Both folders are located in the District records series, New Haven district records subseries.
    - Photographs removed from New Haven district scrapbook, 1971, undated (Box 6, Folder 12)
      Items in this folder were removed from New Haven district scrapbook, 1968-1975, located in the District records series, New Haven district subseries.
  - Southwestern district records, 1967 2010; 1967-2010; 14 Folders
    This subseries contains the records of the Southwestern district, including district officer lists and ballots, mailing lists, lists of event dates, program announcements, meeting programs, annual reports, and officer notebooks. This subseries also contains records pertaining jointly to the Southwestern and Litchfield districts. Until 1973, the Southwestern district was known as the New Haven district, and records of the New Haven district can be found in the New Haven district subseries.
    - Recording secretary notebook, 1967 1997; 1967-1997 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Recording secretary notebook, 1967 1997; 1967-1997 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Treasurer's notebook, 1969 2005; 1969-2005 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Event date lists, 1973 1983; 1973-1983 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Meeting programs, 1973 1998; 1973-1998, undated (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Officer lists, 1973 1999; 1973-1999 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Program announcements, 1973 2006; 1973-2006, undated (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Mailing lists, 1974 1979; 1974-1979 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Officer ballots, 1974 1980; 1974-1980 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Other district records, 1977 2002; 1977-2002, undated (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Board meetings, 1979 1999; 1979-1999, undated (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - District news, 1993 1997; 1993-1997 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Annual reports, 1994 1995; 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Southwestern and Litchfield districts, 2000 2010; 2000-2010 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Financial records, 1941 2020; 1941-2020; 40 Folders; 1 Volume
  This series contains the financial records of the Connecticut Women of the United Church of Christ. Included are treasurers' reports, budgets, charitable fund and gift records, records of fundraising and donations, trust fund records, check registers, bank statements, invoices and receipts, financial correspondence, and a ledger.
  - Check register, 1941 1946; 1941-1946 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Check register, 1947 1950; 1947-1950 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Check register, 1950 1953; 1950-1953 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Check register, 1953 1956; 1953-1956 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Check register, 1956 1958; 1956-1958 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Check register, 1958 1959; 1958-1959 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Check register, 1959 1960; 1959-1960 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Check register, 1959 1963; 1959-1963 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Check register, 1960 1961; 1960-1961 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Check register, 1961 1962; 1961-1962 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Second mile gift, 1945 1964; 1945-1964, undated (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Treasurer's reports, 1945 2020; 1945-2020 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Budgets, 1949 2020; 1949-2020 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Charitable fund records, 1952 1955; 1952-1955 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Windsor Trust Company statements, 1952 1956; 1952-1956 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Invoices and receipts, 1952 1953; 1952-1953 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Invoices and receipts, 1953 1954; 1953-1954 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Invoices and receipts, 1954 1955; 1954-1955 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Invoices and receipts, 1955 1956; 1955-1956 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Invoices and receipts, 1956 1957; 1956-1957 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Invoices and receipts, 1957 1958; 1957-1958 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Invoices and receipts, 1958 1959; 1958-1959 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Invoices and receipts, 1959 1960; 1959-1960 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Invoices and receipts, 1960 1961; 1960-1961 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Invoices and receipts, 1961 1962; 1961-1962 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Invoices and receipts, 1962 1963; 1962-1963 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Fall Conference financial records, 1953 1957; 1953-1957 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - District treasurers' reports, 1953 1959; 1953-1959 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Other financial records, 1955 2006; 1955-2006 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Hartford National Bank and Trust Company statements, 1957 1959; 1957-1959 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Financial correspondence, 1958 1961; 1958-1961, undated (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Offerings, 1959 1989; 1959-1989 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Financial correspondence, 1961 1963; 1961-1963 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Connecticut National Bank records, 1961 1965; 1961-1965 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Ledger, 1961 1968; 1961-1968 (Box 10, Volume 1)
  - Incoming funds records, 1962 1963; 1962-1963 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Information for district treasurers, 1964 1969; 1964-1969 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Itemized receipts and disbursements, 1964 1969; 1964-1969 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Trust fund records, 1968 1969; 1968-1969 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Fundraising and donations, 2011 2019; 2011-2019 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Church Women United in Connecticut contributions, 2013 2015; 2013-2015 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Programming and initiatives, 1944 2019; 1944-2019; 47 Folders
  This series contains records of the programs, events, initiatives, and resolutions of the Connecticut Women of the United Church of Christ. Included are records of conferences, retreats, orientations, trips, services, ceremonies, and other special events; records of service projects and charitable causes; resolution statements in support of special causes; records of efforts to honor lay and clergy women; scripts for plays and pageants; texts of readings, prayers, and liturgies; and event photographs and slides.
  - Other meetings, programs, and events, 1944 2018; 1944-2018, undated (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Church Women United, 1949 1970; 1949-1970 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Other CTWUCC records, 1949 2016; 1949-2016, undated (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Lady Doak College, 1954 1955; 1954-1955 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Photographs, 1955 1989; 1955-1989, undated (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Leadership Training Conference, 1960 1978; 1960-1978, undated (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - International tour, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Plays and pageants, 1964 1970; 1964-1970, undated (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Quiet Day, 1964 1977; 1964-1977 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Readings, prayers, and liturgies, 1964 2002; 1964-2002, undated (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Senexet House retreats, 1965 1973; 1965-1973, undated (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Event date lists, 1964 1994; 1965-1994 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Orientation Day, 1967 1978; 1967-1978 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Silver Lake special projects, 1967 1978; 1967-1978 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Installation service, 1968 1975; 1968-1975 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - National Leaders Come to Connecticut, 1971 1973; 1971-1973 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Library book lists, 1974, undated (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Call on an Elder Training Program, 1977 1980; 1974-1980, undated (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Trip to New York City, 1975 1978; 1975-1978 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Retreats, 1977 2019; 1977-2019 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - National Meeting of Women for Leadership Development, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Coordinating Center for Women in Church and Society, 1987 1988; 1987-1988 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Emmaus "Road to Opportunity" campaign, 1988 1992; 1988-1992 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Red thread project, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Portland, Maine conference photographs, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Portland, Maine conference slides, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Interfaith sewing and service, 1994 2009; 1994-2009 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Honored laywomen, 1995 2014; 1995-2014 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Annual women's luncheon, 1997 1999; 1997-1999 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Haystacks project, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Tie-dyed prayer shawl, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Korean partnership, 2002, undated (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Africa initiative, 2005, undated (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Honored laywomen photographs, 2006 2007; 2006-2007 (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Quilting events, 2007 2015; 2007-2015 (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - First Congregational Church of Greenwich grant program, 2010 2019; 2010-2019 (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Resolution on Women as Equal Partners in Church and Society, 2012 (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - Pioneer women clergy, 2013 2016; 2013-2016 (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - Huguenot cross ceremony, 2016 (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - 90th celebration, 2018 (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - Leadership grant, 2018 (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - Connecticut women CD, 2018 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Connecticut women CD, 2018 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Interfaith prison partnership, undated (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - Resolution in Support of Farm Workers in California Vineyards, undated (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - Resolution in Support of the Boycott of California Table Grapes, undated (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - Signage, undated (Box 7, Folder 63)